Damon Runyon Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Damon Runyon Papers
1876-1985
YCAL MSS 832
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
4.71
(22 boxes) + 15 cold storage, 3 art, 1 broadside folder
The Damon Runyon papers contain correspondence, writings, photographs, scrapbooks, films, and other papers documenting the literary and personal activities of American author Damon Runyon.
Runyon, Damon, 1880-1946
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of William P. Considine, 1985.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
19-33 (reel-to-reel film): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
Alfred Damon Runyon (1884-1946)
Damon Runyon, American journalist and short-story writer, was born 4 October, 1884, in Manhattan, Kansas to Elizabeth and Alfred Lee Runyan, a printer and newspaper publisher. In 1898, Runyon enlisted in the U.S. Army during the Spanish-American War and served in the Philippines. After the war, he worked for a number of newspapers in various small towns in Colorado before he was hired in 1905 as a reporter for the Denver Post. He worked briefly in 1906 as a reporter for the San Francisco Post before returning to Denver to work for the Rocky Mountain News, where he covered sports, crime, and court stories. In addition to his newspaper duties, Runyon wrote short stories and poems for national magazines, including Harper's and McClure's. In 1910, Runyon moved to New York to work as a sportswriter for the New York American. Runyon published a collection of poems, The Tents of Trouble, in 1911, and during the 1920's and 1930's, he published many short stories. In 1932 he published Guys and Dolls, which was made into a popular Broadway musical and film. Motion picture adaptations of two other stories, "The Lemon Drop Kid" and "Little Miss Marker," appeared in 1934. Runyon died 10 December 1946 in New York City.
Biographical information taken from the Guide to Literary Masters & Their Works (January 2007).
Scope and Contents
The Damon Runyon papers contain correspondence, writings, photographs, scrapbooks, films, and other papers documenting the literary and personal activities of American author Damon Runyon. Correspondence consists chiefly of telegrams to Runyon and his second wife, Patrice Amati, from friends and others, and telegrams from Runyon to Patrice dating from the late 1920s through early 1930s. Writings include the work of Damon Runyon, such as drafts of poems and short stories, and writings of others. There are photographs of Damon and Patrice Runyon and numerous American cultural figures from roughly the 1920s through 1940s, including Milton Berle, Jack Dempsey, Al Jolson, Joe Louis, Adele Rogers St. Johns, Walter Winchell, and others. Scrapbooks contain additional correspondence, photographs, and clippings relating to Runyon and his wife, and to Patrice and Richard Coffin. Other materials in the collection include artwork, clippings, financial and legal records, medical and military records, and printed ephemera.
Arrangement
Organied into six series: I. Correspondence, 1918-1980. II. Writings, 1923-1940. III. Photographs, 1888-1967. IV. Scrapbooks, 1917-1980. V. Films, 1933. VI. Other Papers,1876-1985.
American literature -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Audiovisual materials; Photographic prints; Authors -- United States -- 20th Century; Berle, Milton, 1908-2002; Dempsey, Jack, 1895-1983; Jolson, Al, 1886-1950; Louis, Joe, 1914-1981; Runyon, Damon, 1880-1946; Winchell, Walter, 1897-1972
- Correspondence and Other Papers, 1918-1980; Series I; 0.42; (1 box)
  Scope and Contents
  Series I. Correspondence and Other Papers consists chiefly of telegrams to Damon Runyon and his second wife, Patrice Amati, from friends and others, but also includes telegrams from Runyon to Patrice dating from the late 1920s and early 1930s. Other papers include financial and legal records and miscellaneous personal papers.
  - Correspondence: Damon Runyon, A-J, 1923-1944 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Damon Runyon, L-Z, 1918-1941 (Box 1)
  - Wills: Patrice Amati Runyon, 1945, 1968 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Runyon, Patrice Amati, A-Z, 1935-1980 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Runyon, Damon, undated (Box 1)
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati - Resume, 1943, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: McCann, Mary Runyon, 1943-1946 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Gridier, Patrice, 1929-1932,undated; 4 (Box 1)
  - Metcalfe, Jean [Patrice Runyon] portrait, charcoal, undated (Box 1)
  - Runyon, Damon and [Ellen?] invitation, 1919 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Runyon, Damon and Patrice from unidentified people, 1931-1932, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Runyon, Damon and Patrice, A-C, 1931-1932, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Runyon, Damon and Patrice, D-Z, 1932-1944, undated (Box 1)
  - Correspondence: Runyon, Patrice Amati, undated (Box 1)
  - Artist's and Writer's Golf Association card, 1927 (Box 1)
  - Churchill Downs Betting Tickets, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Hialeah Park Owner - Trainer Tax Exempt Clubhouse coupon badge, 1933 (Box 1)
  - Horse Racing Ribbon, undated (Box 1)
  - "Kansas City-Missouri Will Win With Landon..." campaign button, 1936 July 23 (Box 1)
  - Maryland Jockey Club guest badge, 1938 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence of others, A-Z, 1919-1967 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence to Runyon, Patrice Amati from unidentified people, 1931-1967 (Box 1)
  - Republican National Convention, ticket to the press arena, 1934 June 14 (Box 1)
  - Receipts, miscellaneous, 1918-1934 (Box 1)
  - Bills, miscellaneous, 1918 (Box 1)
  - Racing Accounts, 1934-1935 (Box 1)
  - Depositions, 1934, 1936 (Box 1)
- Writings, 1923-1940; Series II; 0.84; (2 boxes)
  Series II. Writings contains writings of Damon Runyon, such as drafts of poems and short stories, and writings of others.
  - Writings of Damon Runyon
    - Miscellaneous notes, autograph manuscript, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Miscellaneous fragments of undeveloped stories, typescript, original and carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Adventures in Nothing Much," poem, typescript, original, corrected, 1923 (Box 2)
    - "A Girl I Used to Know," poem, typescript, mimeograph, corrected, published in the Times Magazine, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Hotshot Kid in the Doghouse," short story, typescript, original, annotated, undated (Box 2)
    - "In Jakey's Place," poem, typescript, mimeographs, corrected, published in The Denver Times magazine, undated (Box 2)
    - "My Bunkie," poem, typescript, mimeograph, corrected, published in the Army and Navy Register, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Old Home," poem, mimeograph, published in The Denver Times Magazine, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Road to Home," poem, typescript, mimeograph, published The Denver Times Magazine, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Song of the Submarine," poem, typescript, mimeograph, published The Denver Post, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Valley of Content," poem, typescript, mimeograph, corrected, published The Denver News, undated (Box 2)
    - Untitled poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated; 2 (Box 2)
    - Untitled short story, autograph manuscript, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - Untitled short story, autograph manuscript, corrected, incomplete draft, with a note, undated (Box 2)
    - Untitled short story, typescript, original, with a note, incomplete draft, 1940 April 23 (Box 2)
    - "Advice," poem, typescript carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Advice (From a Gentleman Inside)," poem, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Antics of Ancestry," short story, autograph manuscript and typescript, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Back to Boyhood," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Ballad of the Third Degree," poem, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Baseball as Big Business," short story, typescript, original, corrected, with a note, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Breeze Kid's Big Tear Off," proofs, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Breeze Kid Sod Fair Salter," short story, typescript, carbon, cottected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "A Broadway Refugee," short story, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Cell House Four," poem, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Chihuahua Upstate Edition... ," [play?], typescript, original, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Christmas Carol," short story, typescript, autograph manuscript, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Confessions of a Sufferagist's Fiance (The Story of a Lost Cause)," short story, typescript, original, corrected, various incomplete drafts, undated (Box 2)
    - "A Cry From the City," poem, typescript, original, corrected, published in the Denver News, undated (Box 2)
    - "D. Cupid; Recruitng [Sergeant]," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Dead That Were Alive," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Evaluation of the Honky-Tonk," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Free Hitter," poem, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Gal (A Letter Home)," poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "God Bless Our Home," short story, typescript, carbon, annotated, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Great Gobble Fish," short story, typescript, original, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Heart's Desire," poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Hike to Pekin," poem, typescript, original, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Hop Fiend," poem, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "How Carlaris Runs," poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "How the War Came to Harlem," short story, typescript, original, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Jails," poem, typescript, original and carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Knights of the Called Bluff," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Law," poem, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Legend of the [Nicrnuaueu's?] Vision and the Burial Pot of Gold," short story, autograph manuscript, corrected, with notes, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Life and Death of Sherman C. Jex," short story, typescript, original, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "A Long Time After Ike Walton," typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Look Out fer Girls," poem, typescript, original, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Man Who Was Too Late," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Marked Man," poem, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Me 'n You," poem, typescript, original, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Measure of Ambition," short story, typescript, original, with note, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "My Old Lady," short story, autograph manuscript and typescript, original, corrected, with notes, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "My Wife 'Ellesi' Hannamaker," short story, typescript, original, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Oh! an' Oh! ab' Oh!," poem, typescript, original, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Outbreak," poem, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Over the Paco," poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Peavey Clegg Army Retired," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Prospector's Thanksgiving," poem, typescript, original, undated (Box 2)
    - "Revenue Without Taxation," essay, typescript, original, undated (Box 2)
    - "Rhyme of the Rum Runner," poem, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Saloon Keeper," poem, typsecript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Saratoga Chips," with Caesr Irving, synopsis, typsecript, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Scourge," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Solitary," poem, typescript, carbon, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Sportsmanship," short story, typescript, original, undated (Box 2)
    - "State of the Nation," article fragment, typsecript carbon, undated (Box 2)
    - "Statement of A. [Muyy?]," short story, autograph manuscript, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Sun Dance Kid Charleroi Dixie Blackmar," short story, typescript, original with a note, undated (Box 2)
    - "Tejon and May Gilseyy," short story, typescript, carbon, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Thanksgiving in the Field," poem, typescript, original, corrected, published in the Denver Times Magazine, undated (Box 2)
    - "Tight Shoes," short story, typescript, original, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Twenty Year Mom," poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "A Typographical Error," short story, typescript, mimeograph, corrected, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "A Typographical Error," short story, typescript, original and carbon, with a note, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Wall Guard," poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "Weighing up the Jury," poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Women Prisoners," poem, typescript, carbon, undated (Box 2)
    - "The Worst Boys in this Town," short story, autograph manuscript, incomplete draft, undated (Box 2)
    - "Yesterday," poem, typescript, original, corrected, undated (Box 2)
  - Writings of Others
    - Unidentified author, "The Runyons," typescript essay, original, undated (Box 3)
    - Breitigam, Jerry, press release, typescript, undated (Box 3)
    - Brymm, J. Tim, "Left Left Behind," sheet music, holograph, undated (Box 3)
    - Perry, Bob, "Tricked," outline, typescript, original, undated (Box 3)
    - McLaurin, Hamish, "The Sheltered Plane," outline of a novel, typescript, original, undated (Box 3)
    - [Mac?]Mahon, Mary, "International Husbands," synopsis, typescript, original, undated (Box 3)
    - Runyon, Patrice Amati, "Footloose and Fancy Free," drafts and fragments, autograph manuscript, corrected, undated; 5 (Box 3)
    - Runyon, Patrice Amati, "Footloose and Fancy Free," drafts, typescript and typescript carbon, corrected, undated; 5 (Box 3)
    - Runyon, Patrice Amati, "R.O.N. Tokyo," typescript, original corrected, original, undated (Box 3)
    - Runyon, Patrice Amati, "Standish Lay," typescript, carbon, corrected, undated; 5 (Box 3)
- Photographs, 1888-1967; Series III; 1.6; (10 boxes)
  Series III. Photographs consists of photographs of Damon and Patrice Runyon and American cultural figures from roughly the 1920s through 1940s, including Milton Berle, Jack Dempsey, Al Jolson, Joe Louis, Adele Rogers St. Johns, Walter Winchell, and others.
  Additional photographs can be found in Series IV. Scrapbooks.
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati, 1956-1967, undated; 3 (Box 4)
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati with dogs, undated (Box 4)
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati with horses, undated (Box 4)
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati with Admiral Deerfield and unidentified man, undated (Box 4)
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati with Mrs. Harold [Keree?], undated (Box 4)
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati with Francis Sargent and unidentified man, undated (Box 4)
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati with Francis Sargent, undated (Box 4)
  - Runyon, Patrice Amati with unidentified people, undated; 2 (Box 4)
  - Wolfson, Patrice Hirsch, 1961 (Box 4)
  - "The World's Richest and Poorest Man," Cleveland, 1912 (Box 4)
  - Runyon, Damon, 1888-1920, undated; 4 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with dogs, 1931, undated; 2 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with unidentified groups of people, undated; 6 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with unidentified man, Lou Itoltz, Ted Husing and Al Jolson, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with "Doyle" [Prihan?], "Mifford," and "Adams", undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Floyd Gibbons, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Tom Heavey, Johnny Risko, and 2 unidentified men, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Mike Jacobs, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with W.F. Kurz and H.I. Morris, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Phil Liebman (Baker), Jack Dempsey, Dick Merrill and Harry Richman, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Joe Louis and unidentified man, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Sen. William Lyons, Jim Coffroth, Mark Kelly, Tommy Laird, and others, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with T. Taggart and John F. Curry, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Bill Corwin and Walter Winchell, 1940 September 26 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Jim Farley, Victor Moore and Al Jolson, 1940 September 26 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Al Jolson, 1940 September 26 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with George McManus, 1940 September 26 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Victor Moore, Al Jolson and Bugs Baer, 1940 September 26 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Wes Peglar, Paul Gallico, Grant Rice and Jack Lait, 1940 September 26 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Bob Ripley, unidentified man, Joe Connolley, Hype Igoe, Bill Corwin and Walter Winchell, 1940 September 26 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon with Nick Kenney, "Broadway Rose," and Milton Berle, 1941 June 17 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon and Patrice, 1934-1941, undated; 5 (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon and Patrice with dogs, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon and Patrice with Mary Elaine Runyon and Damon Runyon Jr., undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon and Patrice with Lord Beaverbrook and Lord McIntyre, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon and Patrice with Bill Dwyer and Mrs. Whitney, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon and Patrice with Harry Richmond, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon and Patrice with Mr. and Mrs. Walter Shirley, Mr. and Mrs. Nate Blumberg, Mr. and Mrs. Leo Spitz, Mr. and Mrs. Pandro Berman and Mr. and Mrs. Jessie Block, undated (Box 5)
  - Runyon, Damon and Patrice with undientified groups of people, undated (Box 5)
  - Unidentified places and things, undated (Box 6)
  - Roof, with Damon Runyon's initials, with a clipping, undated (Box 6)
  - Unidentified people, undated (Box 6)
  - Coffin, Mr. and Mrs. Richard, 1946, undated; 4 (Box 6)
  - Powell, Bill and St. Johns, Adele Rogers, undated (Box 6)
  - Nor' East, Mishaum Point, South Dartmouth, Massachusetts home, 1947, undated; 8 (Box 6)
  - Wedding photographs, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Photographs of [Sevorila Patrice Grideer?], first dancer of the Jay C. Flippen Club, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Miscellaneous group photographs, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Portrait photographs of unidentified woman, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Miscellaneous photographs of Mr. and Mrs. Runyon, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Photograph of Runyons with dog, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Miscellaneous photographs, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Five portrait photographs of unidentified woman [Mrs. Runyon] by Murray Korma, undated (Box 7 (Oversize))
  - Framed photograph of Fourth Annual Artists and Writers Club dinner, 1936 February 16 (Box 8 (Oversize))
  - Framed wedding photograph of Damon and Patrice Runyon, undated (Box 9 (Oversize))
  - Framed portrait photograph of Damon Runyon, undated (Box 10 (Oversize))
  - Framed portrait photograph of [Patrice Runyon?], undated (Box 11 (Oversize))
  - Framed portrait photograph of [Patrice Runyon?], undated (Box 12 (Oversize))
  - Framed photograph of Damon Runyon with unidentified group, undated (Box 13 (Oversize))
- Scrapbooks, 1917-1980; Series IV; 0.6; (5 boxes)
  Series IV. contains three scrapbooks containing correspondence, photographs, and clippings relating chiefly to Damon Runyon, one scrapbook containing material relating to Damon and Patrice Runyon, and one later scrapbook relating to Patrice and Richard Coffin, whom Patrice married following her divorce from Runyon.
  - Scrapbook containing correspondence, photographs and clippings relating to Damon Runyon, 1922-1944, undated (Box 14 (Oversize))
  - Scrapbook containing correspondence, photographs and clippings relating to Richard Coffin, 1946-1970, undated (Box 15 (Oversize))
  - Scrapbook containing correspondence, photographs and clippings relating to the Runyons, 1933-1944, undated (Box 16 (Oversize))
  - Scrapbook containing correspondence, photographs and clippings relating to Damon Runyon, 1926-1980, undated (Box 17 (Oversize))
  - Scrapbook containing correspondence, photographs and clippings relating to Damon Runyon, 1917-1938, undated (Box 18 (Oversize))
- Films, 1917-1980; Series V; (15 cold storage)
  Conditions Governing Access
  19-33 (Cold storage): Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
  Series V. Films appears to consist chiefly of family films, or films relating to Damon and Patrice Runyon, with brief titles possibly referring to horse races from 1933 and family pets.
  - "Damon Runyon Signs Fighters", undated; 35mm film, nitrate (Box 19 (Cold storage))
  - "Traynes, Saratoga", 1933; 16mm film (Box 20 (Cold storage))
  - "Richman Wedding", undated; 16mm film (Box 21 (Cold storage))
  - "Patrice Runyon, 350 W. 57th St., New York City, N.Y.", undated; 16mm film (Box 22 (Cold storage))
  - "Johnny Jacobs", undated; 16mm film (Box 23 (Cold storage))
  - "Saratoga", 1933; 16mm film (Box 24 (Cold storage))
  - "... Tropical, Preakness, Harry...", undated; 16mm film (Box 25 (Cold storage))
  - Untitled 16mm film, undated; 16mm film (Box 26 (Cold storage))
  - "Dogs, Little Puppies, Patrice", undated; 16mm film (Box 27 (Cold storage))
  - "P. Runyon, 21101", undated; 16mm film (Box 28 (Cold storage))
  - ["Father dear & 2..."?], undated; 16mm film (Box 29 (Cold storage))
  - "Mrs. P. Runyon, 213640K" (empty), undated (Box 30 (Cold storage))
  - Three loose untitled film reels in canister, undated; 16mm film (Box 30 (Cold storage))
  - Two loose untitled film reels in canister, undated; 16mm film (Box 31 (Cold storage))
  - Loose untitled 3.5" film reel in canister, undated; 16mm film (Box 32 (Cold storage))
  - Loose untitled 3.5" film reel in canister, undated; 16mm film (Box 33 (Cold storage))
- Other Papers, 1876-1985; Series VI; 1.25; (4 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  Series VI. Other Papers includes artwork, clippings, financial and legal records, medical and military records, and printed ephemera. Clippings contain printed versions of short works by Runyon.
  - Awards and press coverage, circa 1917-1979 (Box 34)
  - Clippings, circa 1876-1977; 7 (Box 34)
  - Discharge papers, 1900 January 4 (Box 34)
  - The Jockey Club certificates, 1932-1937 (Box 34)
  - Kodachrome camera, undated (Box 34)
  - List of "William Considine Gift", circa 1985 (Box 34)
  - Manuscript notes removed from film canisters (In Series V), undated (Box 34)
  - Medical records, 1918-1919, undated (Box 34)
  - Military passes, 1918-1919 (Box 34)
  - Notebook, undated (Box 34)
  - Notice of Personnel Action, 1945 March 5 (Box 34)
  - Pilot log book, 1935 (Box 34)
  - Political rally, Dartmouth High School, 1950 March 4 (Box 34)
  - Clippings, circa 1876-1977; 2 (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Empty frame, undated (Box 35 (Oversize))
  - Framed induction notice for Damon Runyon into the Miami Beach Rod and Reel Club, 1934 December 22 (Box 36 (Oversize))
  - Portrait of Damon Runyon by Robert Whort Joslin, framed, undated (Box 37 (Art))
  - Portrait painting of Damon Runyon, unframed, undated (Box 38 (Oversize))
  - Printed ephemera, undated (Box 39 (Broadside))
  - "Lady Patrice" collage, framed, undated (Box 40 (Art))
  - Portrait of Patrice Runyon with horse, framed, undated (Box 41 (Art))